Guide to the Goldsboro Banyar and Banyar Family Papers 1727-1904 (bulk, 1740-1840) MS 39
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: Goldsboro Banyar
  - Subseries I.5: Patents, deeds and other land conveyances
    This subseries consists mainly of legal documents for the acquisition and conveyance of real property, including Letters Patent (civil and military) and their supporting documents, deeds (generally using the English system of Lease and Release), mortgages, and bankruptcy indentures. Also included are other papers relating to property and estates, such as tenant leases, bonds, surveys, and maps. Most date from two periods: 1761-1775, and the 1790's. The conveyances record Banyar's personal land transactions as well as his legal business with clients, in New York City and Albany, and in upstate New York.
    The majority of the documents are Letters Patent (most with original seals attached) or conveyances and papers relating to them. The Letters Patent, civilian and military, were issued to individuals or, more commonly, to groups, limited in non-military cases to 1000 acres per person but containing totals up to 50,000 acres -- moderate-sized grants compared to those of the 17th or early 18th centuries but substantial nonetheless. Parties to these indentures include many political and business leaders of the pre-Revolutionary era, such as Robert Livingston, John Tabor Kempe, John Morin Scott, Oliver Delancey, John Watts, Peter Van Schaack, James Duane, Alexander Colden, Governor William Tryon, and John Harris Cruger. Some of the post-Revolutionary transactions involve William Cooper, Henry Beekman, and William Lawrence.
    Many of the records relate to New York land grants in Vermont. Often accompanied by papers proving titles, they involve property located in the area East of the Hudson River, then disputed by New Hampshire which later became parts of the state of Vermont. A Commission was established to adjudicate the competing claims, and New York agreed in 1790 to relinquish title to lands in Vermont in return for $30,000.
    The transactions in this subseries illustrate the practices used to accumulate land for speculation, and in some cases give histories of particular lots or parcels in New York City and Albany. There are also many items relating to the military bounties authorized by the Proclamation of October 7, 1763.
    The descriptions in the box and folder list are based on a calendar of the items prepared in the 1970's, which also provides additional background information. This calendar has been included in Box 9A of the collection and is listed at the end of this subseries.
    - Correspondence and papers relating to Samuel Dunlop's settlement of Cherry Valley, 1705, 1736-1764, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and papers relating to Samuel Dunlop's settlement of Cherry Valley, 1766-1774 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Deeds and indentures for land in New York, 1764-1773, 1786, 1792, 1809 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Indentures, surveys and other documents relating to land grants in Vermont, 1760's-1770's (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence and abstracts of letters patent and deeds regarding lands in Vermont, 1767, 1770, 1785-1799 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence and other documents relating to land grants in Vermont, 1761-1773, 1780-1799 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Papers relating to settlement of Vermont lands owned by British army officers (Major Thomas Etherington and Stephen Payne Galwey), 1767-1774, 1785-1789 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Field Book of Edmond Fanning's townships, 1772 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence regarding lands of British General John Vaughan ("Vaughan's Patent"), 1786-1790 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence and papers relating to "Croghan's Mortgage" in Otsego County, 1764-1775, 1795-1804 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Documents relating to settlement of division line between the Wawayanda and Cheesecocks Patents, 1785-1787, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Arbitration of bond and mortgage between Joseph Ketchum and Herman Hoffman, 1765, 1772-1773, 1785-1787 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Releases, leases and deeds for lots in New York City, Albany County and the Hardenbergh Patent, 1728-1754 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 12)
    - Letters patent to Goldsboro Banyar, John Benson, and Joseph Webb for 4000 acres in Albany county; later deed of partition for same 4000 acres, with map entitled "New Dorlach", 1753 April 14, 1793 May 9 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 13)
    - Title deeds, Staley Patent, 1755-1787 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 14)
    - Title deeds, Schuyler Patent, 1755-1793 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 15)
    - Deeds, mortgages and bonds for property in New York City and Albany County, 1759-1769 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 16)
    - Lott's and Magin's Patents, 1761-1763, 1837 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 17)
    - Release-Deed for land in Albany County granted to John Christopher Hartwick, 1761 July 17-18 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 18)
    - Letters patent to Jacob Hendrick, Ten Eyck, George Rykert, Volkert Dason and John Roorbart, Jr. for two tracts of land in Albany County, 1761 September 17 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 19)
    - Letters patent to Alexander Colden and three others for 4000 acres in Albany County, 1761 September 29 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 20)
    - McNeil's Patent, commonly called Otsquage, 1761 September 29-30, 1806 August 21 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 21)
    - Ten Eyck's Patent, 1761 October 1-2, 1793 November 8-9 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 22)
    - Lawyer (Sawyer?) Patent, 1761-1795 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 23)
    - Pittstown Patent and Cambridge Patent, 1761-1769 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 24)
    - Release-deed for three lots within Auchmuty's Patent in Fairfield and Herkimer Counties, 1762 May 7-8 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS25)
    - Releases, leases and deeds for lots in Fairfield, Herkimer, Ulster, and Queens Counties, and in the Hardenburg Patent, 1762-1763 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 26)
    - Letters patent to Thomas Moore and Lewis Pintard for 2 tracts, Orange County, 1762 December 23 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 27)
    - Letters patent to William Cockroft and others for 26,000 acres in Albany County, 1764 May 2 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 27)
    - Title deeds for D. Shaw's Lots in Kingsbury, 1764 September 20-24 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 28)
    - Letters patent (military) and assignments/conveyances of soldiers' rights, 1765-1774 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 29)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in New York and Vermont, 1765-1772 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 30-37)
    - Letter patent (military) for land in Vermont, 1765 July 25, 26 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 38-39)
    - Letters patent to Frederick Young and 19 others for 20,000 acres in Cherry Valley and Sharon, Otsego and Schoharie Counties, 1765 October 11 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 40)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in New York and Vermont, 1766, 1768 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 41-45)
    - Vermont deeds and claims, 1768-1798 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 46)
    - Title deeds, 3 lots & buildings in Albany ("Shipboy lot"), 1768-1804 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 47)
    - Bankruptcy paper, assignment by Isaac Man of all personal real property in trust for payment of debts, 1768 September 19 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 48)
    - Deeds for land in township of Blenheim, 1769 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 48)
    - Alexander Stewart's original deeds, Otsego County, 1769 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 49)
    - Deeds for lots in Cosby's Manor, 1769, 1795 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 50)
    - Title to lands in Vermont, 1769-1798 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 51)
    - Letters patent to Garret Slover & 13 others in Vermont, 1769 November 8 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 52)
    - Letters patent to John Wetherhead, John Tabor Kempe, and 38 others in Blenheim township, 1769 November 28 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 53)
    - Letters patent to Pierre G. DePeyster and others for land to be erected into a township named Kempeton (Vermont), 1769 November 24 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 54)
    - Deeds for land in township of Kempeton, 1769-1770 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 55)
    - Deeds for land in township of Warrentown (Vermont), 1769-1770 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 56)
    - Deeds for lots in township of Kent (Vermont), 1770, 1774 (Box OS medium, Folder OS 57)
    - Title deeds, Nettlefield/Loudon Patent (Decatur, Otsego County), 1770, 1773, 1792 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 58)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in Vermont, 1770 April 5 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 59)
    - Deeds and patents for land in Vermont, 1766 May 2 - 1775 August 29 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 60)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in Vermont, 1770 April 6 (Box Oversize small, Folder Banyar OS 60A)
    - Letters patent for lots in Readsborough Township (Vermont), 1770 April 24 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 61A)
    - Deeds for lots in Readsborough Township (Vermont), 1770 June 11 - 1797 May (Box OS medium, Folder 61)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in Durham, Greene County, 1770 May 17 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 62)
    - Deed for lot in township of Kelso (Vermont), 1770 May 23-24 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar O 63)
    - True copy of letters patent (military) for land in Albany County (Vermont), 1770 June 1 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 63)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in Gloucester county (Vermont), 1770 April 5 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 64 - 68)
    - Return of survey for tracts in Gloucester County (Vermont), 1770 April 4 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 68A)
    - Title Deeds, Goldsborough Township, Delaware County, 1770 June 8 - 1801 June 4 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 69)
    - Letters Patent, Goldsborough Township, Delaware County, 1770 April 30 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 69A)
    - Certificate for setting out a grant, Goldsborough Township, Delaware County, 1770 April 20 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 69B)
    - Letters Patent for lands purchased from Indians, Goldsborough Township, Delaware County, 1770 June 15 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 69C)
    - Letters patent (military) for land in Rome, Oneida County, 1770 May 2 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 70)
    - Letters patent, Wallace's Patent (Sidney, Delaware County), 1770 June 16 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 71A)
    - Title deeds, Wallace's Patent (Sidney, Delaware County), 1770 June 9 - 1799 January 4 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 71)
    - Letters patent, Belvidere Patent (Cherry Valley, Otsego County), 1770 June 29 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 72A)
    - Title deeds, Belvidere Patent (Cherry Valley, Otsego County), 1770 June 18 - 1772 February 27 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 72)
    - Copy of Letters patent to Peter Muerenbeldt and others for land in Vermont, 1770 June 1 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS73)
    - Letters patent to Jacobus VanZandt and others for land in township of Newbrook (Vermont), 1770 June 13 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS74)
    - Deed from John Wilson and Henry Boel to Goldsboro Banyar for land in township of Newbrook (Vermont), 1770 July 20-21 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS73)
    - Deed from James Seagrove and William Gillylan, Jr. to Goldsborough Banyar for land in township of Kingsborough (Vermont), 1770 June 28-29 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS73)
    - Deed from Samuel Boyer and Peruke Maker to Goldsborough Banyar for land in Whitingham township (Massachusetts), with maps, 1770 July 11, undated (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS75)
    - Deed and lease with Whitehead Skidmore and others for land in Jamaica, Queens, 1770 July 12-13 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS76)
    - Deed from Isaac Ogden and others to William Kelly for land in township of Gageborough (Vermont), with related documents, 1770 August 11 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS77)
    - Deed from John Abeel and others to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Township of Hutton (Vermont), 1770 August 21 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS78)
    - Deed from George Etherington and others to Goldsboro Banyar for land in the township of Dunmore (Vermont), 1770 August 20-21 (Box Oversize medium, Folder Banyar OS78)
    - Deed from Charles Morse and William McAdam to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Saratoga County, 1770 August 29-30 (Box Oversize medium, Folder Banyar OS78)
    - Letters patent (military) to Norman McLeod for land on north side of Mohawk River (probably Fulton County) (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS79)
    - Deed from Peter Silvester and Mydert Roseboom to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Cherry Valley, Otsego County, 1770 October 24-25 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS80)
    - Deed from Peter Soutenberg and John Voorheese to Goldsboro Banyar for land in township of Kent (Vermont), 1771 January 28-29 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS80)
    - Deed between Cuyler family members for dwelling and store house on the east side of Pearl Street, 1770 October 19 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS80A)
    - Deeds to and from Abner French for land near Schenectady, 1770 March 17, 1772 April 21 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS80A)
    - Letters patent (military) to Alexander Graydon of Dublin for land in Cumberland County (Vermont), 1770 October 4 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS81)
    - Deed from Alexander Graydon to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Cumberland County (Vermont), 1770 November 1-2 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS81A)
    - Letters patent (military) to John Clark for land in Vermont, 1771 March 9 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS82)
    - Draft of Letters patent (military) to John Clark, 1771 March 9 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS82A)
    - Deed from William Wood to John Wetherhead for land in Schoharie County, 1771 March 16 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS83)
    - Indenture from Peter Martin and his wife Mary to Eilhu Hall Bay for land on Flat's Island and elsewhere, 1771 March 30 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS83)
    - Deed between Joseph Rodman, John Badeau and John Fitzpatrick for land and premises in New Rochelle, 1771 March 29-30 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS83)
    - Deed from John Kelly to Crean Brush for land in the township of Readesborough (Vermont), 1771 April 2-3 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS83)
    - Letters patent (military) to Thomas Mason for land in Putnam, Washington County, 1771 April 8 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS84)
    - Conveyance of soldier's rights from Thomas Mason to Philip Skene, 1769 May 12 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS84A)
    - Deeds for the Commissioner on Vermont Claims, Albany, 1771 April 9 - 1772 January 2 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS85)
    - Letters patent (military) to James Scott and Hugh Jackson, disbanded soldiers for land in Warren County, 1771 May 24 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 86)
    - Certificate for setting out land grant and deeds for township of Fincastle, 1771 May 27, June 27-29 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 87)
    - Deeds for land in "Franklin's patent" (Otsego and Schoharie Counties), 1771 May 29-30, 1791 September 22 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 88)
    - Tenant lease to Daniel Hucker, Gold and Silver Smith, and John Sebastian Stephany, Chemist, for 99 years for land in Duchess County, 1771 June 1 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 89)
    - Letters patent to William Bayard and 54 others for land in Oneida and Herkimer counties, 1771 June 12 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 90)
    - Certificates for setting out land grants issued to William Bayard and William Shirreff, 1771 April 22, 30 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 91)
    - Letters patent to William Shirreff and 22 others for land in the township of Halesborough (Vermont), 1771 April 22 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS92)
    - Deeds from Charles Morse to Goldsboro Banyar for land in township of Deerfield (Vermont), 1771 June 22 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS93)
    - Copy of deeds from William Haldane for land near Wood Creek, 1771 June 1, 21-22, November 1 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS93)
    - Letters patent to John Davan and 23 others for land in the township of Richmond (Vermont), 1771 June 28 (Folder OS medium, Folder Banyar OS94)
    - Certificate for setting out land grant issued to John Davan and leases from Davan to Banyar, 1771 June 26, July 12-13 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS95)
    - Letters patent to William McAdam and 29 others for land in the township of Kilby, 1771 July 3 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS96)
    - Deeds for land in township of Kilby, 1771 July 25, 30-31 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS97)
    - Letters patent (military) to Samuel Dick, late Surgeon's Mate at His Majesty's Military Hospital, for land in Vermont, 1771 July 6 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS98)
    - Deeds for land in Leinster and Mecklenbergh townships, 1771 July 17-18, September 6-7 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS99)
    - Mortgage and lease from John Kelly to Goldsboro Banyar, 1771 September 10-11 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS100)
    - Letters patent to John Butler and 39 others for land to be erected into a township called Strasburgh (Schoharie County), 1771 December 4 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS101)
    - Certificate for setting out a grant in Strasburgh township issued to John Butler and 39 others, 1771 August 30 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS102)
    - Letters patent to William Nicholls and 5 others for land in Vermont, 1772 March 3 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS103)
    - Certificate for setting out a grant issued to William Nichols, 1771 September 6 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS104)
    - Deeds from William Nicholls to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Vermont, with map showing partition of land, 1772 March 16-17 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS104)
    - Letters patent to Thomas Barnet and others for land to be erected into the township of Penryn (Virginia), 1772 March 10 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS105)
    - Certificate for setting out a grant in Penryn township issued to Thomas Barnet, 1772 February 19 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS102)
    - Letters patent (military) to Thomas Millet, Philip Lambert and Robert Davidson, disbanded soldiers, for land in Albany County (Greene County), 1772 March 10 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS106)
    - Deeds for land on the west side of the Hudson River (Greene County), 1772 March 21, 24 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS107)
    - Deeds for land in Truro Township (Vermont), 1772 April-June (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS108)
    - Letters Patent to Edward and Ebenezer Jessup for land in Luzerne, Warren County, 1772 April 10 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS109)
    - Deed from Nathan Stone to GB for land in Windsor (Vermont), 1772 April 18 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS110)
    - Deeds for land in the township of Penryn (Vermont), 1772 April-June (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS111)
    - Deed from Charles Nicholl and 3 others to William Banyar, 1772 June 16-17 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS112)
    - Letters patent to Andrew Elliot and 20 others for land in county of Charlotte (Vermont), 1772-1773 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS113)
    - Letters patent to Crean Brush, John Grumly and Joseph Beck for land in Bolton, Warren County, 1772 October 24 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS114)
    - Tripartie Agreement settling estate in new trustees, 1773 March 12 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS112)
    - Deeds for property in Montgomery Ward, New York City, 1771, 1773 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS115)
    - Deed from Joseph Blancard to Joseph Griswold, Distiller and Abraham Nelson, Merchant, for land in Durham, Greene County, 1773 July 22 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 112)
    - Lease for plot in Township of Royalton; Mortgage from Thomas Valentine to GB on property in Charlotte County, 1773 August 6-7, November 11 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS116)
    - Indenture between William William and Goldsboro Banyar for land in township o Readsborough, 1774 January 25-26 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS117)
    - Indenture between John Church and Edmond Tanning or land in Cumberland County, 1774 February 3-4 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS117)
    - Mortgages from John Cattleman and Peter Davy to James Delancey, 1774 June-July (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS117)
    - Indentures between Frederick Rhinelander and Duncan Campbell/Thomas Hobson, 1774 March-April (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS118)
    - Letters patent (military) to Duncan Campbell for land in Totten and Crossfield's Purchase, 1774 April 5 (Box OS small, Folder OS119)
    - Letters patent (military) to William Markham for land in Totten and Crossfield's Purchase, 1774 April 5 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS120)
    - Letters patent to Luke Knoulton and 19 others for land in the township of Kellybrook (Vermont), 1774 July 20 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS121)
    - Deeds for land in township of Kellybrook, 1774 August 24-25 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 122)
    - Deed to Duncan Campbell for share in Totten and Crossfield's Purchase, 1774 September 19 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 123)
    - Deeds for land in township of Rutland, 1774 September 14, 21-22 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 124)
    - Deeds for land in township of Meath (Vermont), 1775 January-March (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 125)
    - Letters patent to Josiah Willard and 24 others for land in township of Meath (Vermont), 1775 February 11 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 126)
    - Letters patent to Lt. John Thompson for land in Charlotte County (Vermont), 1775 June 19 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 127)
    - Letters patent to Saumel Ashley and 25 others for land in township of Smithfield, 1775 June 21 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 128)
    - Deeds for land in township of Smithfield, 1775 June-August (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 129)
    - Indenture of Peter Van Schaack's property to his children, 1778 August 14 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 130)
    - Tripartite Indenture (Marriage Settlement) of Stephen Payne Gallway, Oliver Delancey, and Phila Delancey, 1774 December 8; 1786 June 2 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 130)
    - Letters patent to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Montgomery County, 1786 July 11 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 131)
    - Deed of partition with map of Banyar's patent, 1796 August 9 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 132)
    - Letters patent to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Bergen's Purchase (4 patents), 1786 July 1786 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 133-136)
    - Letters patent to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Delaware County (7 patents), 1786 August 14 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 137-143)
    - Mortgage and leases from Thomas Mears to Goldsboro Banyar for land in Montgomery County, 1786 October 27-28, 1802 February 11 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 144)
    - Deed from Goldsboro Banyar to John Coleman, Innholder, for Moiety of a farm in Orange County, 1792 June 4 (Box OS large, Folder Banyar OS 145)
    - Deed for land in England (William Banyar), 1791 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 146)
    - Mortgages relating to George Clarke, 1795 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 146)
    - Deeds for land in Arthursboro, Otego and Phelps and Gorham townships, 1796-1797, 1806-1807 (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 147)
    - Summersvale, Refuge and Chase's Patent, 1804, 1806, 1826 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 148)
    - Deeds for land in Dutchess County (Robert Livingston) (Box OS medium, Folder Banyar OS 149)
    - Deeds relative to Harbeck lots (Albany), 1786-1820 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 150)
    - Deeds for land in Albany (include Church Pew rental), 1795, 1798, 1802-1803 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 151)
    - Deeds for land in Albany, 1813-1815 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 153)
    - New York City deeds, 17906, 1803, 1809-1816 (Box OS small, Folder Banyar OS 154)